Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2000; 15 Linear Feet 22 boxes containing 458 items.
  - Personal or Unidentified, 1973-1999
    - Undated, ?something [unidentified woman, mostly background noise]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0291)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0291_01.wav)
    - Undated, lundi 12 Mars [women's demonstration in French]
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0292)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0292_01.wav)
    - Circa 1980, March on Washington/Gay Freedom Train
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0293)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0293_01.wav)
  - Recordings of Family, 1984-1988
    - 1984, Mother speaks, Mallory's tape
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0294)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0294_01.wav)
    - 1986 May, Aunt Mig
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0295)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0295_01.wav)
    - 1987, Aunt Mig, Xmas
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0296)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0296_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0296_02.wav)
    - 1988 Nov., Trying to tape Mother Millett, 1988 November
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0297)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0297_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0297_02.wav)
    - Undated, Mom's Tape for Kate
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0298)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0298_01.wav)
    - Undated, Mom's Tape for Kate, 2nd try
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV8, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0299)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0299_01.wav)
    - Undated, Aunt Mary, second session, Oct. 19, on Ampex
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0300)
    - Undated, Mother Speaks - My trip around the world; Funny things my children did
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0301)
    - Undated, Aunt Mig
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0302)
  - Recordings of Others, 1980-1998
    - Scots folk, circa 1980
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0303)
    - Jeffrey Masson and Peter Breggin on psychiatry and the Holocaust, National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA convention, 1988)
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0304)
    - Analysing Psychiatry, 1990 Nov. 5, 1990 November 5
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0305)
    - Judi Chamberlin and Sally Zinman, Historical Perspective on Movement, NARPA convention, 1990
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0306)
    - Dr. Peter Breggin, Toxic Psychiatry, radio talk shows, 1990 Nov. 10 and 13, 1990 November 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0307)
    - Peter Moritz Pickshaus - Valerie Solanas,"Scum," 1998
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0308)
    - Music, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0309)
    - Dr. Elizabeth Kubler-Ross on death [recording from radio], undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0310)
    - Dr. Elizabeth Kubler-Ross on death [recording from radio], undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0311)
    - Scots folk for Sophie, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0312)
    - 8237 Psychiatric Drugs/Bio, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0313)
    - 8237 Psychiatric Drugs/Bio, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0314)
    - Alexandra de Lallier talks about Kate's work and the goddess, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0315)
    - Ed Podvoll, M.D., Creating a Sane Asylum, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0316)
    - Laurie Ziegler, Mad Liberation Movement, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0317)
    - Closetland soundtrack, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0318)
    - Closetland soundtrack, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0319)
    - Kate Simpkins poetry, 1998
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0320)
  - 1974 Recordings
    - Black Irish on Black - to be printed with oration, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0321)
    - Jim Smith, prison class [interviews?], undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0322)
    - Herbert Marcuse on feminist Socialism, Stanford Univ., 1974 Mar. 8, 1974 March 8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0323)
    - Berkeley women write and excerpts from Flying, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0324)
    - Folsom Ride, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0325)
    - Douglas Halford and James Smith, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0326)
    - The emptiness, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0327)
  - Torture interviews, 1987
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0328)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0329)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0330)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0331)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0332)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0333)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0334)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0335)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0336)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0337)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV9, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0338)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0339)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0340)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0341)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0342)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0343)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0344)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0345)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0346)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0347)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0348)
    - Interviews, San Francisco and Mexico, 1987 Apr.-Aug. and undated, 1987 April-August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV10, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0349)
  - Recorded Book Drafts
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0350)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0351)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0352)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0353)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0354)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0355)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0356)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0357)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0358)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0359)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0360)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0361)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0362)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0363)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0364)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0365)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0366)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0367)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0368)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0369)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0370)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0371)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0372)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0373)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0374)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0375)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0376)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0377)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0378)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0379)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0380)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0381)
    - Loony-Bin Trip, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV11, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0382)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0383)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0384)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0385)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0386)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0387)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0388)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0389)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0390)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0391)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0392)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0393)
    - A.D., undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0394)
    - Kate reads Aunt Dorothy, part 3, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0395)
    - End of Kate reads AD #3, undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0396)
    - 1st, 2nd and 3rd readings, Aunt Dorothy, 1984 Aug., 1984 August
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV12, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0397)
  - Mixed Material, 1975-1999
    - 1980 Democratic Convention notes [water damaged], 1980
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0398)
    - Notes separated from recordings, 1992-1997 and undated
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0399)
    - Herbert Marcuse and Kate Millett, "Dialogue on Feminism" - cassette tape and correspondence, 1975
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0400)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0400_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0400_02.wav)
    - Smith College interview, "Starting the Movement" - cassette tape and correspondence, 1997
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0401)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0401_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0401_02.wav)
    - Conversation with Phyllis Chesler and Eleanor Pam on the Farm and Kate's future - cassette tape and notes, 1992 Apr., 1992 April
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0402)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0402_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0402_02.wav)
    - Interview - cassette tapes, partial transcript, and correspondence with interviewer Diane Gallagher, 1995
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0403)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0403_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0403_02.wav)
    - Interview - cassette tapes, partial transcript, and correspondence with interviewer Diane Gallagher, 1995
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0404)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0404_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0404_02.wav)
    - Interview - cassette tapes, transcript, and correspondence with interviewer Elizabeth Fishel, 1978
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0405)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0405_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0405_02.wav)
    - Interview - cassette tapes, transcript, and correspondence with interviewer Elizabeth Fishel, 1978
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0406)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0406_01.wav)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0406_02.wav)
    - Amy Frazer, song "My Name is Sylvia Likens" - cassette tape and correspondence, 1997
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0407)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0407_01.wav)
    - BBC Woman's Hour program - cassette tape and correspondence, 1999
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0408)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL10070-SET-0001, Audio-file RL10070-CS-0408_01.wav)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0409)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0410)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0411)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0412)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0413)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0414)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0415)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0416)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0417)
    - National Association for Rights Protection and Advocacy (NARPA) Annual Meeting, Strategies for Change Now!, cassette tapes and conference schedule, 1990 Nov. 7-8), 1990 November 7-8
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV13, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0418)
    - Irish nite [sic] tape #2, ending of it all - open reel tape and notes, undated
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL10070-RR-0001)
    - New Orleans/ Florida trip - "Philosophy Night at Century Village" cassette and travel materials, 1998
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0419)
    - Rae Unzicker, National Alliance of Mental Patients - cassette and information packet, 1987
      - Original audiocassette (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL10070-CS-0420)
    - Torture, Iran, interview in Paris - microcassette tape and note, undated
      - Original microcassette (Box AV14, Audio-cassette RL10070-MCS-0001)
  - Phonograph Records, 1974; 16
    - Disc 1: England Dan and John Ford Coley, Big Tree Records BT-16069, 1974, 423
      - Original phonodisc (Box AV15, Audio-phonodisc RL10070-PD-0001)
    - Disc 2: Margie Adams, "Well, I Never" custom cut disc and correspondence, 1974 Oct.-Nov., 424
      - Original phonodisc (Box AV15, Audio-phonodisc RL10070-PD-0002)
  - Audio Tapes, 1970-1980; 17
    - Tape 1: "Kate then Naruda begins 120", undated; 425
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0002)
    - Tape 2: "Aug. 5 Old Time Reading to Purge Self - Tennyson and Browning", undated; 426
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0003)
    - Tape 3: Irish talk - Norman Irish Knights brigade, undated; 427
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0004)
    - Tape 4: Unfinished petition to U.N. against executions, undated; 428
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0005)
    - Tape 5: McCormick report and convention aftermath, master, 1980 Aug. 13-14, 1980 August 13-14; 429
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0006)
    - Tape 6: Kate at L.A. Fat Lady show for Sylvia White film, day of or just before the opening, interview and public reaction, 1977 Mar., 1977 March; 430
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0007)
    - Tape 7: Irish night, undated; 431
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0008)
    - Tape 8: Kate reads Yeats for Aunt Dorothy, 1980 June 20, 432
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0009)
    - Tape 9: Kate reads Yeats? [may be blank], undated; 433
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0010)
    - Tape 10: Basement tape for Michael Korda, undated; 434
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0011)
    - Kate's copy of Sophie's Scots Folk/ Kishmael's Galley, Lustrafe Song, Kate's whistling recorded 1st world premier - recorded quatro, 1980 Sept. 12, 1980 September 12; 435
      - Original 1/4-inch open-reel audiotape (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL10070-RR-0012)
    - Kate reads on St. Patrick's night, Bowery - Iran, great mach, Daddy Book, 1980, 436